Interviewer: What are you doing in Oxford today?
Anna: I’m here visiting a friend and just looking around.
Interviewer: What clothes do you usually wear for work?
Iain: I wear semi-formal clothes, so a shirt and trousers,
but I don’t need to wear a tie.
Interviewer: Would you like to live in England?
Jayna: Yes.
Interviewer: Why?
Jayna: The history of the place, and just, um,
it really is a beautiful country.
Interviewer: Are you staying in a hotel?
Sandra: Yes.
Interviewer: Do you like it?
Sandra: Yes, I like it very much.
Interviewer: Why?
Sandra: It’s situated near the river, it’s really nice and cosy,
they serve pints in the evening, so we’re fine.
Interviewer: Where were you at ten o’clock last night?
Spencer: At ten o’clock last night I was in my hotel room.